http://www.themoneyalert.com/privacy-policy/

AllCalculatorsCareerCollege PlanningCreditTaxes
4 Questions To Answer – What Career Is Best For Me?
Steps to Becoming a Certified Public Accountant (CPA)
Elevator Pitch Writing Tips & Examples
10 Tips From A Recruiter For Crafting Your LinkedIn Profile Summary
Credit
Understanding Your Credit Score Rating Scale Range
What is a Tri-Merge Credit Report?
How to Remove Derogatory Items From Your Credit Report
What is a Credit Supplement?
The Difference Between Soft Pull vs Hard Pull Credit Checks
Career
4 Questions To Answer – What Career Is Best For Me?
Steps to Becoming a Certified Public Accountant (CPA)
Elevator Pitch Writing Tips & Examples
10 Tips From A Recruiter For Crafting Your LinkedIn Profile Summary
Understanding Property Taxes
What is Depreciation?
Understanding Section 1035 Exchange Rules
401K Loan: A Good Idea?
401k Withdrawal: Having Access to your Future
IRA Rollover Rules
Required Minimum Distribution (RMD)
Economics
Elliott Wave Theory Explained
Financial Ratios Defined
The Stock Market Crash of 1929
Understanding Consumer Price Index (CPI)
Gross Domestic Product (GDP)
Real Estate
AllMortgage
What is an FHA 203(k) rehab loan?
Understanding VA Loan Requirements
Converting a Construction Loan to Permanent Financing Process
What is a Credit Supplement?
Mortgage
What is an FHA 203(k) rehab loan?
Understanding VA Loan Requirements
Converting a Construction Loan to Permanent Financing Process
What is a Credit Supplement?
How to Get a Land Loan
Legal
AllEstate Planning
What Does an Estate Planning Attorney Do?
What Is a Trust Fund and How Does It Work?
What is a Revocable Living Trust?
What Is an AB Trust?
Estate Planning
What Does an Estate Planning Attorney Do?
What Is a Trust Fund and How Does It Work?
What is a Revocable Living Trust?
What Is an AB Trust?
What is a Last Will and Testament?
Insurance
What Is an Irrevocable Life Insurance Trust (ILIT)?
Legal Malpractice Insurance Basics
Universal Life Insurance Planning
Annuities Explained
Is an Immediate Annuity Right for You?
Privacy Policy
The Money Alert takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it. You can learn about privacy policies in general by doing a search on the topic.
Routine Information Collection
All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.
Cookies and Web Beacons
Where necessary, The Money Alert uses cookies to store information about a visitor’s preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.
Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other
useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection. An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website. These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Controlling Your Privacy
Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.
Special Note About Google Advertising
Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Google’s cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google’s own privacy policies.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Contact Information
Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to our Contact Us page for further clarification.
MOST POPULAR
How to Write a Winning Resume
August 24, 2018
Weekly Stock Market Commentary 1 19 2009
June 29, 2018
Sallie Mae Student Loans
June 29, 2018
Dividing Assets In A Divorce
June 29, 2018
Load more Personal Finance
AllCalculatorsCareerCollege PlanningCreditTaxes
4 Questions To Answer – What Career Is Best For Me?
Steps to Becoming a Certified Public Accountant (CPA)
Elevator Pitch Writing Tips & Examples
10 Tips From A Recruiter For Crafting Your LinkedIn Profile Summary
Credit
Understanding Your Credit Score Rating Scale Range
What is a Tri-Merge Credit Report?
How to Remove Derogatory Items From Your Credit Report
What is a Credit Supplement?
The Difference Between Soft Pull vs Hard Pull Credit Checks
Career
4 Questions To Answer – What Career Is Best For Me?
Steps to Becoming a Certified Public Accountant (CPA)
Elevator Pitch Writing Tips & Examples
10 Tips From A Recruiter For Crafting Your LinkedIn Profile Summary
6 Critical Steps to Landing Your Dream Job
College Planning
IRA for College: A College Planning Quandary
529 A Prepaid Education
Sallie Mae Student Loans
College Costs: The University of Ouch
529-Mania
Taxes
Estate Tax / Inheritance Tax & Gift Taxes
What is a Tax Shelter
Understanding Property Taxes
What is Depreciation?
Tax Tables / Tax Bracket Rates 2018
Investing
AllEconomicsRetirement Planning
Understanding Section 1035 Exchange Rules
Selling Restricted and Insider Stock
Best CD Savings Rates
Annuities Explained
Retirement Planning
Understanding Section 1035 Exchange Rules
401K Loan: A Good Idea?
401k Withdrawal: Having Access to your Future
IRA Rollover Rules
Required Minimum Distribution (RMD)
Economics
Elliott Wave Theory Explained
Financial Ratios Defined
The Stock Market Crash of 1929
Understanding Consumer Price Index (CPI)
Gross Domestic Product (GDP)
Real Estate
AllMortgage
What is an FHA 203(k) rehab loan?
Understanding VA Loan Requirements
Converting a Construction Loan to Permanent Financing Process
What is a Credit Supplement?
Mortgage
What is an FHA 203(k) rehab loan?
Understanding VA Loan Requirements
Converting a Construction Loan to Permanent Financing Process
What is a Credit Supplement?
How to Get a Land Loan
Legal
AllEstate Planning
What Does an Estate Planning Attorney Do?
What Is a Trust Fund and How Does It Work?
What is a Revocable Living Trust?
What Is an AB Trust?
Estate Planning
What Does an Estate Planning Attorney Do?
What Is a Trust Fund and How Does It Work?
What is a Revocable Living Trust?
What Is an AB Trust?
What is a Last Will and Testament?
Business
Business Ownership Structures
Business Types of Ownership
Buy Sell Agreement
How to Write a Business Plan
Incorporating: Setting Up a Corporation
Insurance
What Is an Irrevocable Life Insurance Trust (ILIT)?
Legal Malpractice Insurance Basics
Universal Life Insurance Planning
Annuities Explained
Is an Immediate Annuity Right for You?
More
Tables
Estate Tax / Inheritance Tax & Gift Taxes
Tax Tables / Tax Bracket Rates 2018
C Corporation vs S Corporation vs LLC Table
Social Security Benefits Table 2018
RMD – Required Minimum IRA Distribution
Calculators
Glossary
Quarterly Market Commentary
Weekly Market Commentary
EDITOR PICKS
Inflation vs. Deflation
June 29, 2018
401K Loan: A Good Idea?
June 29, 2018
IRA and 401k Contribution Limits
June 29, 2018
POPULAR POSTS
RMD – Required Minimum IRA Distribution
June 29, 2018
How to Protect Yourself from Identity Theft [Today]
July 24, 2018
C Corporation vs S Corporation vs LLC Table
June 29, 2018
POPULAR CATEGORYWeekly Market Commentary115Investing67Personal Finance56Retirement Planning56Insurance53Real Estate40Quarterly Market Commentary36Estate Planning31Mortgage30
OUR PURPOSEWe are on a mission to provide highly reliable financial advice without bias or outside influence. Focusing on all topics as they relate to your personal finance needs. Well researched planning topics include retirement planning, investing, real estate, legal and more.
Contact UsFOLLOW US
Privacy Policy
Disclaimer
Contact Us
Copyright © 2006 - 2020 The Money Alert Personal Finance. All Rights Reserved.
